{
    "id": "45153aa390c5408f8795261e8ebab315",
    "title": "Present Continuous Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Hurry up! We ……………………….. for you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "waiting",
                "are waiting",
                "wait"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "‘What are you ……………………….?' ‘I ………………………. letters.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "doing, writing",
                "done, writing",
                "doing, write"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………. in Italy at the moment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "works",
                "working",
                "is working"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn’t like to be disturbed when she …………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "works",
                "working",
                "is working"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "That child ……………………………… bigger everyday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gets",
                "getting",
                "is getting"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is that girl …………………………….. on the table?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stand",
                "standing",
                "is standing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………….. for the shops to open.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wait",
                "am waiting",
                "waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………….. Jane tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "am seeing",
                "seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The universe ………………………, and has been so since its beginning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "expands",
                "is expanding",
                "expanding"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister ……………………. at home for the moment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lives",
                "living",
                "is living"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}